[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The beagle is not a good choice for a childrens pet because it is aggressive.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did popcorn originate?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Chicago", "Columbia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are cardiac arrhythmias?", "correct_answer": "Abnormal rhythms of the heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Whistling or swishing sounds", "How fast your heart is beating", "Normal rhythms of the heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2002 movie The Ring is not a remake.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1997 movie was this line delivered: Never believe what you publish, and never publish what you believe.?", "correct_answer": "The Night Flier", "incorrect_answers": ["Wolf", "Village of the Damned", "I Know What You Did Last Summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Since 1815, Switzerland has been involved in only a few wars because of its policy of neutrality.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies did not win 11 Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Braveheart", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King", "Titanic", "Ben Hur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cocktail was reportedly the first drink the American astronauts had when they returned to Earth in 1969.", "correct_answer": "Moonwalk", "incorrect_answers": ["Daiquiri", "Bloody Mary", "Pina Colada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This reef, that extends along the east coast of Australia, is home to countless animals and is considered one of the wonders of the natural world.", "correct_answer": "Great Barrier Reef", "incorrect_answers": ["Division Reef", "Australia Reef", "Surfer Reef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jacob, the most popular boys name of 2006, means one who fishes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Koalas almost exclusively feed on this type of food.", "correct_answer": "Eucalyptus leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Bottle tree leaves", "Tea tree leaves", "Bamboo leaves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first female Attorney General of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Janet Reno", "incorrect_answers": ["Joanne Pierce", "Susan Roley", "Clarisa Starling"]}]